[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 15]
I'm here!
Don't run.
♫How many rain seasons and rains do I need to see♫
If I wake up,
♫Before meeting you♫
I'm not gonna see you again.
No.
♫I am destined to sink to the bottom of the sea♫
Because...
♫You come to my mind♫
Is Luo Ge you, too?
Lu Li is me.
♫But this moment, you believe♫
Luo Ge is me, too.
♫You are my only one. Don't hesitate♫
Wherever you are,
I'll be there.
♫Flowers fly after the rain♫
♫I stay there♫
This is the Lu Li on earth.
♫I say I miss you. Because of your name♫
♫The rest of my life is all about you♫
♫I can't tell if it is dream♫
♫After the flower blossoms, let the love go on♫
♫I say I miss you. Don't doubt it♫
♫You exist in my life♫
♫I want to stay with you♫
♫After the spring and the winter, let the love go on♫
So when I went through my ordeal on earth,
the person I met was you.
You admitted that
you're Lu Li?
You just...
forgot, right?
I don't need to remember.
Whatever I have experienced on earth, people or things,
or false love,
are just doom and gloom.
Since it's doom,
there's no need to look back.
I don't believe it.
You don't believe it?
Even if Lu Li did die,
even if his death
was so painful that it made the heart bleed,
I would like to look back on
my experience with him a million times.
Without these experiences,
my life
would have been pale and boring.
And the best thing
that ever happened to me
was that I met him.
Mortals are ridiculously fragile.
It's because of this obsession
that you're trapped in your dreams by Luo Ning's scent.
But I'm so happy now.
Because...
you're still alive.
All right.
I'm not him.
I advise you to go with the flow,
and stay away from love, hate, delusion and anger.
Don't waste yourself on me.
People can't stay away from love, hate, delusion and anger.
What's so good about being a clay fairy without a heart?
You're
quite special.
Come to Palace Chonghua
in four hours.
Bai Feng, don't worry.
Within three days,
your internal wounds will be healed.
But
we just became friends.
You're leaving again.
Liu Shao said
Lu Li might still be alive.
I can't just go back to earth.
If you come next time,
we'll get together again.
Okay.
Thank you.
Master.
Who is that?
He seems to be popular with his disciples.
-That's Immortal Luo Ge's master. -You have a good talent.
-Immortal Master Wanwu. -Practice with your heart.
There's a good chance that Immortal Luo Ge will become a god.
Then Immortal Master Wanwu's position
would be very different.
Very different?
Become a god?
General Xie.
Well,
he has
a human face.
I can't believe he broke
a thousand years of rules.
That's ridiculous.
He's the only upper immortal in the Three Realms.
If it hadn't been for the Immortal Palace's compassion,
you wouldn't have stayed to heal.
You're just a mortal.
Don't you dare say that
in Immortal Palace.
Is it reasonable
for you to discredit the Immortal?
-Immortal Master Wanwu. -Immortal Master Wanwu.
How dare you
stand up to General Xie.
Aren't you afraid of death?
All I know is that
the Immortal was born for the Three Realms
and can't be discredited.
Beyond this,
I'm not afraid of anything.
You!
I like
her very much.
She can stay.
But,
you're going to start with my court chores.
Will you?
I will do anything.
I'm finally here.
Oh, no.
To enter the Palace Chonghua,
I have to break a formation?
Formation?
Ge.
What were you thinking?
Since we want to leave her in the Xiyin Mountain,
we must test her patience and understanding.
All we need
is her blood.
Restoring the Four Seasons Monument
and protecting the peace of the Three Realms
are the real compassion for all living beings.
But Liu Shao is one of them.
We should never give up
unless we have to.
Besides, even if we use up Liu Shao's blood,
we may not be able to restore the Four Seasons Monument.
But if she has the skill to break the formation,
I have a plan,
making a blood amulet.
Blood amulet?
Okay.
Lu Li.
You still have 15 minutes.
You!
Ouch!
Who...who...who?
Who dares to beard the lion in his den?
Gosh,
Liu Shao!
Master!
What are you doing here?
I...
So many things have happened.
The Four Seasons Monument changed because of you?
The new Immortal
is Lu Li?
I think he's Lu Li.
But...
He's not like Lu Li.
Lu Li wouldn't do it to me,
and he wouldn't do it to anyone else.
So he went to earth to experience hardships?
Now he has no earthly memory.
He didn't know you,
so he gave you the cold shoulder.
But it's old wine in a new bottle.
The flowers and leaves are replaced but the roots remain the same.
Isn't he the same guy?
Girl.
Lu Li
is the one who holds you close to his heart.
It's not something you can give up if you want to.
Even if he wants to,
I won't let him give up.
Isn't Lu Li him?
Anyway.
What we said before
doesn't count?
I will definitely make him like me again,
at least he can remember me again.
That's the Liu Shao I know.
Palace Chonghua is close at hand.
I don't believe I can't get through.
That's right.
The mutated Five-Element Formation
is also a Five-Element Formation.
Yes.
I'm sure
you can break this formation.
Remember,
Lu Li's formation was taught by Lu Sheng.
I've only learned a little,
but,
it's enough.
Five pillars are based on wood.
Therefore,
this five elements formation is centered on wood.
I used fire to restrain gold,
but it was restrained by water.
I can
use wood to release water
to make a fire.
In the end,
I used wood as a constraint.
Earth grew with gold.
Water and earth are disconnected.
The fire can fetch gold directly.
How is this formation gonna stop me?
Let's go.
I came here on time.
Immortal!
Is it okay to do this?
Yes.
Immortal!
I came here on time.
We're coming in.
Why is there no one here?
Immortal!
Immortal, are you there?
I think
he's hiding
because he saw you fall and didn't picked you up.
You think too much.
Girl.
What is it?
Why does this tree grow upside down?
Where is its roots?
How much better can a tree be when it's off the ground?
It's all alone.
Girl,
do me a favor.
Water this dude.
This is Immortal's palace.
I dare not.
Take it back.
If you take good care of the tree,
he won't blame you.
Listen to me. It can't be wrong.
Really?
Okay.
Im... Im...Immortal.
We... we have no other intention.
We just want to water the tree.
This is Xuan Ling Wood.
It's nourished by the immortal power.
It doesn't need rain and dew.
Of course,
it doesn't need your watering.
You're the new gardener
of the Xiyin Mountain?
You really are Lu Li.
The willows of Xiyin Mountain have been dead for a hundred years.
But because of you,
they came back to life.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Planting trees and flowers
is my favorite.
Please take care of
the flowers and trees of the Xiyin Mountain.
No problem.
Would you please leave?
I have something to say to Liu Shao.
Go, go, go.
Go.
Immortal,
what do you want me to do here?
You have Sun's power.
The blood in you can repair the Four Seasons Monument.
You know that, right?
I didn't know this before.
Now I know.
So?
Are you going to drain my blood
to repair the Four Seasons Monument?
Even if I drained your blood,
it may not be enough to repair it.
So?
I'm going to plant a blood amulet on you,
using your blood and energy
to make the talisman pearl.
And then I'll take out the talisman pearl
to repair the Four Seasons Monument.
Would that have any effect on my body?
It doesn't matter to take one or two out.
If you take out four or five, you're going to be very weak.
If we take seven out,
the restoration of Four Seasons Monument will be assured.
But you...
will die.
Well...
How many do you need?
Well.
I can't decide until I see how effective the talisman pearls are.
If it doesn't work,
you'd really take seven out
and kill me?
You can disagree.
But if the Four Seasons Monument is ever in danger,
you'll be sacrificed for blood.
And you'll have no chance of survival.
This is
your compassion?
I pity all beings, but you are only one of them.
If you are lucky enough,
one day you'll get the talisman pearls back.
And you'll be as good as ever.
It seems I have to say yes.
Then promise me one thing.
What is it?
Your palace
won't stop me.
I can come and go as I please.
I know you like to be quiet.
But if you want to make me into talisman pearls,
I'm afraid my days here are numbered.
Okay.
I promise you.
But you must abide by
my rules.
Please go ahead.
There are three things you can't do.
First,
Xuan Ling Wood can't be touched.
Second,
the books in the palace can't be touched.
Third,
and
most important,
I
can't be touched,
even a shadow or a piece of clothing.
Do you understand?
I will follow your rules.
But please promise me one condition.
Go ahead.
Don't blame Luo Ning for the scent in my dream.
It's all my obsession.
She just wanted to help me.
That's all?
Okay.
So many scriptures!
Copy them all?
My brother
told you to bring them to me?
Yes.
He also said this time was different.
You can't copy this book
until you've made the words disappear.
How... How can I
copy out the words from the scripture?
Don't you know how to do magic?
You can cast spells.
Right.
How could I forget?
Okay.
Well.
Let me think.
Try... Try again.
Okay.
It didn't work?
Did Luo Ge ban these books?
Why can't this work?
Or Luo Ning's magic didn't work?
Liu Shao.
How about...
How about you go back and talk to my brother?
Let him think of something else.
He won't listen to me.
But, I can still help you.
Have you seen all these before?
Yes,
and I've copied them many times.
But...
But what good is that?
I'm not interested in them at all.
And I soon forget the content.
Love brings sorrow.
The word is gone.
Yes!
I get it.
Only when the words are really in your heart
will they disappear.
I see.
Liu Shao.
I think
this all seems
pretty easy to you.
How about this?
Do me a favor.
I need you to recite all this for me.
So I can talk to my brother.
Okay? Liu Shao.
Luo Ning.
Do you want
the dew of the King Herb?
The dew of the King Herb?
Yes! Yes!
Tell me where it is.
Okay, but...
You have to memorize it first.
Don't worry.
I'll do it with you.
You... you're done?
[Meditation Spell]
Why did Senior Zhuo come to Xiyin Mountain again?
Master Shang
must have sneaked out again.
Master Shang?
Yes.
Let me tell you.
The master of three palaces, Shang Yurong,
is flashy
and at loose ends all day.
So,
you have to be careful
and stay away from him.
Okay.
[Palace of Abyssal Mirrors]
Let's hurry up.
We'll be waiting at the Litian Temple later.
The canonization of the Immortal is about to begin.
Okay, I get it.
Shang Yurong!
Get out here!
General Zhuo.
Where is Master Shang?
He went out early in the morning.
Did he not know that
the canonization ceremony was to take place this morning?
He's the head of three palaces.
He has to be there.
Yes...yes.
Then why is he hiding?
Go.
Bring me
his favorite dress inlaid with gold silk
and the sea pearl crown.
General Zhuo.
Tell your master
he must be at the Litian Temple
when the auspicious time comes.
Otherwise,
I'm sure
he won't be able to wear a single piece of yarn.
I finally finished memorizing.
Liu Shao.
You're so nice.
I've finally finished memorizing these books.
Thank you.
But if it hadn't been for me,
you wouldn't have been punished by the Immortal.
So it's all about sharing the good
and the bad.
Let's look for the dew.
Let's go.
Wait.
Liu Shao.
I don't want to look for the dew now.
Why don't we go to the Litian Temple together?
Today
is the day of my brother's canonization.
Let's go together.
Luo Ge will be promoted to the Immortal?
Let's go together, okay?
So Lu Li will be an Immortal?
There hasn't been an immortal in thousands of years.
Why isn't Rong here yet?
It's a blessing for the Immortal Palace.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
There's only one immortal in a thousand years,
so the ceremony has to be huge.
The Immortal is about to be canonized.
On such an important day,
as the head of three palaces,
I can't believe Shang Yurong didn't show up.
That would be pretty humiliating for the Immortal.
Master Shang has been so busy practicing recently
that he can't help losing track of time.
The Immortal is coming,
but Master Shang isn't here.
Who will be in charge?
He's right.
Now Luo Ge is an Immortal.
Can Shang Yurong
still sit at the top?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Can't you see that?
Shang Yurong
is no match for
the Immortal.
If it hadn't been for former Master Shang's favoritism,
I'm afraid he wouldn't have been able to maintain
his position as the master of the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors.
Now Shang Yurong is the head of the three palaces,
but he hasn't even learned
the Burning Sea of the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors.
How does this reassure
the dead master?
I advise you to tread lightly.
To criticize the master of the palace
is to violate the immortal rules.
You overreacted.
I don't think I'm breaking the rules
by telling the truth.
I'm just
happy for Luo Ge
because he got promoted.
What are you trying to say?
Everyone,
with Luo Ge's ascension to Immortalhood,
I think the whole Immortal Palace needs to change.
For example,
the position of the head of the three palaces
should be replaced by a competent man.
I won't argue with you
on this day of the Immortal's canonization.
If you don't stop talking like that,
I won't go easy on you.
Oh,
I was right?
You don't want to change the master?
Is that true?
Yes.
The Immortal really should have chosen someone else to be the master.
Otherwise, the millennia of the Immortal Palace's legacy
would be ruined.
The throne of the three palaces is not for you to judge.
Ridiculous!
Then I would like to ask you
where is
Abyssal Mirrors Palace's
noble master?
[Shang Yurong, Master of the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors]
Go!
Luo Ning.
Looks like she took too long memorizing last night.
But this...
What am I supposed to do?
Who are you?
Miss, are you going to the Litian Temple in the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors?
Yes.
I know the way.
I'll take you there.
But I don't even know who you are.
What does that matter?
This is the Immortal Palace,
the most peaceful and boring place in the world.
And I'm so well-dressed.
I'm not a bad person, okay?
All right.
Thank you.
By the way,
you don't seem to know how to sail.
Let me teach you.
Okay.
That will do.
Yes, that's it. Not bad.
You go a little further to the left.
A little more to the left.
No, no, no.
To the right.
Okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's it.
Yes, yes.
To the left.
Left.
You!
Shang Yurong!
Don't you dare tell us what to do.
I'll go to the Palace Wuxie
and tell your Senior Zhuo.
Ning, you woke up just in time.
Here, look at me.
Is such a beautiful scene
a perfect match
for my gorgeous golden feather garment?
So,
you kept telling me to adjust the angle
to suit
your outfit?
Yes.
What?
You've gone too far.
I'm gonna go back and tell my brother.
The Palace of Abyssal Mirrors is the head of the three immortal palaces.
And I'm the master.
I'm not afraid of your brother.
Liu Shao.
What you don't know is that
this guy
has been practicing the Burning Sea for 500 years
without success,
which got his Senior Zhuo
ridiculed by Xie Lingqi.
Don't you dare compare yourself to my brother.
What? Xie Lingqi?
He dared to laugh at my senior sister?
I wonder if the ceremony is about to begin?
Will we be late?
No, no.
Ignore him.
Have a seat.
Master Shang is too busy practicing
to come here.
On behalf of the master, I'd like to propose a toast to you.
May God bless the Abyssal Mirror.
Who said Master Shang wasn't coming?
Immortal Master.
Master Shang told me that
since three palaces wanted to congratulate the Immortal,
the gift
should be shared by three palaces.
Sister Zhuo, please open this box first.
Why is she here?
It's inappropriate, isn't it?
I can't believe she showed up at this big event.
General Xie.
Please read out the words on the scroll
so that the ceremony is complete.
Why me?
It's Master Shang's request.
Well,
can't you read?
I...
Immortal
Shang
Yu
Rong
arrives.
I, Shang Yurong, the head of three palaces,
led the Immortal Palace
to greet Immortal.
Immortal.
I'm from Xiyin Mountain.
She's the one I need to protect.
Congratulations, Immortal.
Your body is glassy
inside and out.
You demonstrate your ideas by acting on them.
We are clean together.
Congratulations on your promotion.
From now on, your grace is all over the world.
The Three Realms are at ease.
I, Luo Ge,
wish to benefit the Three Realms
and the people.
I would like to be the way to all beings.
I would like to give all
in exchange for the clarity of the world.
Yes.
This is my senior.
She is in charge of Palace Wuji,
responsible for the rules and regulations.
The Thunder Whip in her hand is for evil creatures.
This is Immortal Wanwu, the Master of Palace Wuji,
responsible for the suppression of evil and expeditions.
As for
the other affairs of the Immortal Palace,
the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors is in charge.
So
the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors is the head of the three palaces?
Smart.
What about Palace Chonghua?
The three palaces do not include Palace Chonghua.
Luo Ge devoted himself to practice
and became an immortal.
Of course, Palace Chonghua
is more otherworldly.
Come here.
Get up, get up, get up.
Behind.
Have a seat.
Me? Can I?
Yes.
Sit down.
I don't think it's appropriate.
What's wrong with this?
I don't think that's appropriate.
This is the feast of the Immortal.
She's just a mortal.
What qualifies her to sit?
Sit down.
Well,
if Liu Shao wants,
she can be my wife.
Shang Yurong!
Do you know what you are saying?
There has to be a limit to willfulness.
Sit down.
I don't care
if she's mortal or immortal.
All I know is that
Liu Shao has promised to use herself to make the blood amulet
to repair the Four Seasons Monument.
I want to ask who in this room
can do that.
Tomorrow I'll lay out a magic circle on Lusitai
and use Liu Shao's body
for the blood amulet.
I'm willing to help you
defend the magic circle.
No need.
Disciples of the Three Immortal Palaces
are not allowed to go near Lusitai
for three days.
Yes.